George M. Gray Museum Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- 35mm Slide Collection, Series I
  - Localities., 002023
    - Penikese Island. Across Scirpus marsh toward Tub Point. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., 002133
    - Penikese Island. Agassiz Laboratory. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., 002145
    - Penikese Island. Agassiz Laboratory. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., 002146
    - Pilings. Pilings. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002104
    - Pocasset. Cobbles, Wings Neck. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Aug 1965; 002254
    - Pocasset. Cobbles, Wings Neck. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Aug 1965; 002255
    - Pocasset. Rock shore, Wings Neck. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Aug 1965; 002256
    - Pocasset. Rock association, Wings Neck. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Aug 1965; 002257
    - Pocasset. Rock association, Wings Neck. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Aug 1965; 002258
    - Pocasset. Rock association, Wings Neck. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Aug 1965; 002259
    - Pocasset. Eelgrass, 8'. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Oct 1965; 002260
    - Pocasset. Mud bottom, 6'. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Oct 1965; 002261
    - Pocasset. Mud bottom, 7'. Massachusetts: Bourne, Pocasset., Oct 1965; 002262
    - Provincetown. Hatches Harbor. Massachusetts: Provincetown., 01 Jul 1965; 002263
    - Provincetown. Dunes, Race Beach. Massachusetts: Provincetown., 01 Jul 1965; 002264
    - Provincetown. Dunes, Race Beach. Massachusetts: Provincetown., 01 Jul 1965; 002265
    - Provincetown. Behing second dunes, Race Beach. Massachusetts: Provincetown., 01 Jul 1965; 002266
    - Provincetown. Exposed roots of a Bayberry Colony, Race Beach. Massachusetts: Provincetown., 01 Jul 1965; 002267
    - Quivett Creek Marsh. Quivett Creek Marsh. Massachusetts: Dennis., 24 Jun 1965; 002081
    - Quivett Creek Marsh. Quivett Creek Marsh. Massachusetts: Dennis., 24 Jun 1965; 002082
    - Salt Marsh. Salt marsh. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002099
    - Salt Marsh. Salt marsh. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002100
    - Salt Marsh. Salt marsh. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002101
    - Salt Marsh. Salt marsh. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002102
    - Salt Marsh. Salt marsh. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002103
    - Salt Marsh. Salt marsh and creek with Ammophila sp., Aug 1966; 002048
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty, 5' deep. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002073
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty, 5' deep. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002074
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002075
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002076
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002077
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002078
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002079
    - Sandwich Jetty. South side Sandwich Jetty. Massachusetts: Sandwich, Cape Cod Canal., Aug 1965; 002080
    - Sandwich. Beach. Massachusetts: Sandwich., Apr 1967; 002268
    - Sandwich. Beach, low tide. Massachusetts: Sandwich., Dec 1967; 002269
    - Scorton River. Scorton River. Massachusetts: Barnstable., Apr 1967; 002065
    - Shoreline. Shoreline. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002105
    - Shoreline. Shoreline. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002106
    - Shoreline. Shoreline. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002107
    - Shoreline. Shoreline. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002108
    - Shoreline. Shoreline. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002109
    - Surf. Surf. Massachusetts: Cape Cod., 002051
    - Trees. Trees showing effects of wind and spray., Aug 1966; 002047
    - Wareham. Hurrican precautions. Massachusetts: Wareham., Sep 1955; 002270
    - Weepecket Islands. Herring gulls. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., Aug 1966; 002180
    - Weepecket Islands. Herring gulls. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., Aug 1966; 002181
    - Weepecket Islands. Herring gulls. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., Aug 1966; 002182
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull chick. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., Jun 1969; 002179
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002147
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002148
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002149
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002150
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002151
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002152
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002153
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese eggs hatching. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002154
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese eggs hatching. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002155
    - Weepecket Islands. Canada geese eggs hatching. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002156
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant nests. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002157
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant nests. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002158
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant nests. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002159
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant nests. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002160
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant nests. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002161
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant nests. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002162
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant nests. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002163
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002164
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002165
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002166
    - Weepecket Islands. Comorant chicks. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002167
    - Weepecket Islands. Mallard duck. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002168
    - Weepecket Islands. Mallard duck eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002169
    - Weepecket Islands. Gulls. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002170
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002171
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002172
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002173
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002174
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull eggs. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002175
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull eggs hartching. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002176
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull chicks. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002177
    - Weepecket Islands. Gull chicks. Massachusetts: Weepecket Islands., May 1969; 002178
    - Woods Hole. Waterfront. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 1948; 002272
    - Woods Hole. Waterfront. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 1948; 002273
    - Woods Hole. Approach from the Hole. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 1953; 002274
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor and USFW service. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 1953; 002275
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor, visit of NY Yacht Club. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 1955; 002276
    - Woods Hole. Aerial view from Green Pond towards Woods Hole. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 1956; 002271
    - Woods Hole. Algal Zonation, Fisheries. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1954; 002281
    - Woods Hole. Eel Pond, anticipating Hurricane Daisy. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1958; 002279
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Light and hurrican flags. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1958; 002292
    - Woods Hole. SS Martha's Vineyard aground in the Hole. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1961; 002280
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Point, sand bottom, 4'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1964; 002295
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Point, sand bottom, 5'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1964; 002296
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor, mud bottom, 15'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1965; 002285
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor, mud bottom, 15'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1965; 002286
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor, mud bottom, 15'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1965; 002287
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor, mud bottom, 15'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1965; 002288
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor, mud bottom, 15'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1965; 002289
    - Woods Hole. Great Harbor, mud bottom, 10'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1965; 002290
    - Woods Hole. From Nobska Light towards Falmouth. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Aug 1978; 002293
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Light. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Feb 1966; 002294
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Point, rock association. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jul 1965; 002298
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Point, rock association. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jul 1965; 002299
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Point, rock association. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jul 1965; 002300
    - Woods Hole. Site of Fisheries residence. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jun 1958; 002277
    - Woods Hole. Site of Fisheries lab. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jun 1958; 002278
    - Woods Hole. Pump dock piling, 5'. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jun 1965; 002283
    - Woods Hole. MBL dock piling, 2 m. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jun 1965; 002284
    - Woods Hole. Little Harbor, flounder in shallow water. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jun 1965; 002291
    - Woods Hole. Pump dock piling. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., Jun 1966; 002282
    - Woods Hole. Nobska Point, Algal zonation. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 002297
    - Woods Hole. Lillie Building, rear view from Eel Pond. Massachusetts: Falmouth, Woods Hole., 002304
    - Xanthoria. Xanthoria rock association. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002115
    - Xanthoria. Xanthoria rock association. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002116
    - Xanthoria. Xanthoria rock association. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002117
    - Xanthoria. Xanthoria rock association. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Jul 1967; 002118
    - Yarmouth. Chapin Memorial Beach, eroding dunes, beach plum shrubs. Massachusetts: Yarmouth., 24 Jun 1965; 002301
    - Yarmouth. Chapin Memorial Beach, flats. Massachusetts: Yarmouth., 24 Jun 1965; 002302
    - Yarmouth. Chase Garden Creek. Massachusetts: Yarmouth., Jun 1965; 002303
    - Zonation. Zonation. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002110
    - Zonation. Zonation. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002111
    - Zonation. Zonation. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002112
    - Zonation. Zonation. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002113
    - Zonation. Zonation. Massachusetts: Hadley Harbor., Aug 1965; 002114
  - People., 002025
    - Andrew L. Driscoll & Robert H. Parker. Andrew L. Driscoll & Robert H. Parker, Canlde House, MBL., Sep 1964; 002440
    - Andrew L. Driscoll. Andrew L. Driscoll., Jan 1965; 002439
    - Arno J. Bowden. Arno J. Bowden., Oct 1965; 002417
    - Arno J. Bowden. Arno J. Bowden., Oct 1965; 002418
    - Barry A. Wade. Barry A. Wade., Jun 1966; 002621
    - Barry A. Wade. Barry A. Wade., Jun 1966; 002622
    - Barry A. Wade. Barry A. Wade., Sep 1965; 002620
    - Barry Martin. Barry Martin., Oct 1965; 002477
    - Betsy Palmer, Bruce W. Found & P. Orsen. Betsy Palmer, Bruce W. Found & P. Orsen. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002501
    - Bruce W. Found & Donald J. Zinn. Bruce W. Found & Donald J. Zinn. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002444
    - Bruce W. Found. Bruce W. Found. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002443
    - Constance A. Brackett. Contance A. Brackett, SEP office, MBL., Feb 1970; 002419
    - Constance A. Brackett. Contance A. Brackett., Jan 1971; 002422
    - Constance A. Brackett. Contance A. Brackett., Jul 1970; 002420
    - Constance A. Brackett. Contance A. Brackett., Jul 1970; 002421
    - David C. Grant. David C. Grant. Massachusetts: Woods Hole., Mar 1965; 002446
    - David C. Grant. David C. Grant. Massachusetts: Woods Hole., Mar 1965; 002447
    - David C. Grant. David C. Grant., May 1965; 002448
    - David C. Grant. David C. Grant., Nov 1964; 002449
    - David C. Grant. David C. Grant., Nov 1964; 002450
    - David C. Grant. David C. Grant., Nov 1964; 002451
    - David C. Grant. David C. Grant., Sep 1965; 002445
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002637
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002638
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002639
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002640
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002641
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002642
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002643
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002644
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002645
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002646
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002647
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002648
    - David K Young. David K Young, subsurface buoy., 02 Mar 1967; 002649
    - David K. Young & David C. Grant. David K. Young & David C. Grant. Massachusetts: Buzzards Bay, Sta. R., Jul 1967; 002635
    - David K. Young & David C. Grant. David K. Young & David C. Grant. Massachusetts: Buzzards Bay, Sta. R., Jul 1967; 002636
    - Diane C. Johnson. Diane C. Johnson., Oct 1965; 002476
    - Dirk Van Zandt. Dirk Van Zandt., Dec 1965; 002617
    - Donald J. Zinn, et al. Donald J. Zinn, Bruce W. Found, betsy Palmer and Janis Speel. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002656
    - Donald J. Zinn, et al. Donald J. Zinn's group. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002657
    - Donald J. Zinn, et al. Donald J. Zinn's group. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002658
    - Donald J. Zinn, et al. Donald J. Zinn's group. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002659
    - Donald J. Zinn. Donald J. Zinn. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002652
    - Donald J. Zinn. Donald J. Zinn. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002653
    - Donald J. Zinn. Donald J. Zinn. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002654
    - Donald J. Zinn. Donald J. Zinn. Massachusetts: Penikese Island., Aug 1967; 002655
    - Donald J. Zinn. Donald J. Zinn., Jul 1966; 002650
    - Donald J. Zinn. Donald J. Zinn., Jul 1967; 002651
    - Edmund H. Smith. Edmund H. Smith., May 1965; 002573
    - Edmund H. Smith. Edmund H. Smith., May 1965; 002574
    - Edwin T. Moul, Diana Eldridge & Hilary Williams. Edwin T. Moul, Diana Eldridge & Hilary Williams. Massachusetts: Monomoy Island., Jul 1965; 002490
    - Edwin T. Moul. Edwin T. Moul., Jul 1966; 002488
    - Edwin T. Moul. Edwin T. Moul., Jul 1966; 002489
    - Edwin T. Moul. Edwin T. Moul. Massachusetts: Yarmouth, Chapin memorial Beach dunes., Jun 1965; 002487
    - Eva S. Montiero. Eva S. Montiero., Dec 1965; 002481
    - Eva S. Montiero. Eva S. Montiero, SEP office, MBL., Feb 1970; 002484
    - Eva S. Montiero. Eva S. Montiero., Jan 1971; 002485
    - Eva S. Montiero. Eva S. Montiero., Jan 1971; 002486
    - Eva S. Montiero. Eva S. Montiero., Oct 1965; 002482
    - Eva S. Montiero. Eva S. Montiero., Oct 1965; 002483
    - Gerald E. Walsh. Gerald E. Walsh., 1965; 002623
    - Gerald E. Walsh. Gerald E. Walsh., 1965; 002624
    - Gerald E. Walsh. Gerald E. Walsh., 1965; 002625
    - Gerald E. Walsh. Gerald E. Walsh., 1965; 002626
    - Gerald E. Walsh. Gerald E. Walsh., Nov 1964; 002627
    - Gerald E. Walsh. Gerald E. Walsh., Nov 1964; 002628
    - Gerald E. Walsh. Gerald E. Walsh., Nov 1964; 002629
    - H. Suzanne Bolton. H. Suzanne Bolton, research assistant to Dr. Grant., Sep 1967; 002416
    - Hazel F. Santos. Hazel F. Santos., Feb 1965; 002530
    - Hazel F. Santos. Hazel F. Santos., Oct 1964; 002528
    - Hazel F. Santos. Hazel F. Santos., Oct 1965; 002529
    - Hilary Williams. Hilary Williams., Dec 1964; 002632
    - Hilary Williams. Hilary Williams., Jul 1965; 002631
    - Hilary Williams. Hilary Williams., May 1965; 002633
    - Hilary Williams. Hilary Williams., Sep 1965; 002634
    - Horace W. Stunkard. Horace W. Stunkard., Aug 1970; 002577
    - J. Stewart Nagle & Robert H. Parker. J. Stewart Nagle & Robert H. Parker, Candle House, MBL., Aug 1964; 002491
    - J. Stewart Nagle & Robert H. Parker. J. Stewart Nagle & Robert H. Parker, Candle House, MBL., Aug 1964; 002492
    - J. Stewart Nagle. J. Stewart Nagle., Jan 1965; 002493
    - J. Stewart Nagle. J. Stewart Nagle., Jan 1965; 002494
    - Jack B. Pearce. Jack B. Pearce., May 1965; 002517
    - Jack B. Pearce. Jack B. Pearce., May 1965; 002518
    - James Fiore. James Fiore., Sep 1970; 002441
    - James Fiore. James Fiore., Sep 1970; 002442
    - James M. Heller. James M. Heller., Jul 1965; 002467
    - James M. Heller. James M. Heller., Jul 1966; 002468
    - James P. Ostergard & David Grant. James P. Ostergard & David Grant. Massachusetts: Cape Cod Bay., Mar 1966; 002508
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., Dec 1965; 002507
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., Jul 1966; 002510
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., Jul 1966; 002511
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., Jun 1966; 002509
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., May 1965; 002502
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., May 1965; 002503
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., May 1965; 002504
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., May 1965; 002505
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard., Nov 1965; 002506
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard aboard R/V A.E. Verrill., Sep 1967; 002512
    - James P. Ostergard. James P. Ostergard aboard R/V A.E. Verrill., Sep 1967; 002513
    - James R. Sears. James R. Sears., Mar 1967; 002546
    - Janis A. Speel. Janis A. Speel., Jul 1966; 002575
    - Joan R. Conway & William J. Woelkerling. Joan R. Conway & William J. Woelkerling., Dec 1969; 002435
    - Johanna M. Reinhart. Johanna M. Reinhart., Dec 1967; 002522
    - Johanna M. Reinhart. Johanna M. Reinhart., Dec 1967; 002523
    - Johanna M. Reinhart. Johanna M. Reinhart., Jan 1971; 002526
    - Johanna M. Reinhart. Johanna M. Reinhart., Sep 1967; 002524
    - Johanna M. Reinhart. Johanna M. Reinhart., Sep 1967; 002525
    - John C. Carter. John C. Carter., Jan 1965; 002431
    - John C. Carter. John C. Carter., Jan 1965; 002432
    - John C. Carter. John C. Carter., Jan 1965; 002433
    - John J. Valois, et al. John J. Valois, Paul A. Shave, Peter J. Oldham, David C. Grant and James P. Ostergard., May 1965; 002616
    - Joseph L. Simon & Kay W. Petersen. Joseph L. Simon & Kay W. Petersen., Sep 1964; 002565
    - Joseph L. Simon, Stuart L. Santos & B. Wood. Joseph L. Simon, Stuart L. Santos & B. Wood., Oct 1965; 002551
    - Joseph L. Simon, et al. Joseph L. Simon, Johanna M. Rinhart, Janis A. Speel & Keith M. Border., Jul 1967; 002553
    - Joseph L. Simon, et al. Joseph L. Simon, Victor A. Zullo, Stuart L. Santos & Barry A. Wade., Oct 1965; 002554
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon., Aug 1965; 002566
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon, diving test., Jul 1965; 002556
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon, diving test., Jul 1965; 002557
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon, diving test., Jul 1965; 002558
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon, diving test., Jul 1965; 002559
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon, diving test., Jul 1965; 002560
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon, diving test., Jul 1965; 002561
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon., Jul 1965; 002562
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon trip., Jul 1967; 002552
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon trip. Massachusetts: Martha's Vineyard, off Gay Head., Jul 1967; 002555
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon., Mar 1967; 002563
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon., Mar 1967; 002564
    - Joseph L. Simon. Joseph L. Simon., Sep 1965; 002567
    - Katharine Cram & Susan Tracy. Katharine Cram & Susan Tracy., Aug 1964; 002436
    - Katharine Cram, Susan Tracy & Peter E. Schwamb. Katharine Cram, Susan Tracy & Peter E. Schwamb., Aug 1964; 002437
    - Katharine Cram. Katharine Cram., Dec 1965; 002438
    - Katharine D. Hobson. Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002469
    - Katharine D. Hobson. Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002470
    - Katharine D. Hobson. Katharine D. Hobson, MBL., May 1967; 002471
    - Kay W. Petersen. Kay W. Petersen., Sep 1964; 002519
    - Kay W. Petersen. Kay W. Petersen., Sep 1964; 002520
    - Kay W. Petersen. Kay W. Petersen., Sep 1964; 002521
    - Leif Stormer. Leif Stormer., 002576
    - Linda Rogers & Peter E. Schwamb. Linda Rogers & Peter E. Schwamb., Jul 1966; 002527
    - Louise F. Bush. Louise F. Bush. Massachusetts: Dennis., Jun 1967; 002424
    - Louise F. Bush. Louise F. Bush. Massachusetts: Dennis., Jun 1967; 002425
    - Louise F. Bush. Louise F. Bush. Massachusetts: Dennis., Jun 1967; 002426
    - Louise F. Bush. Louise F. Bush., May 1965; 002429
    - Louise F. Bush. Louise F. Bush., Sep 1970; 002427
    - Louise F. Bush. Louise F. Bush., Sep 1970; 002428
    - Melbourne R. Carriker. Melbourne R. Carriker., Feb 1970; 002430
    - Norman R. Sinclair & Horace W. Stunkard. Norman R. Sinclair & Horace W. Stunkard., Aug 1970; 002569
    - Norman R. Sinclair & Horace W. Stunkard. Norman R. Sinclair & Horace W. Stunkard., Aug 1970; 002570
    - Norman R. Sinclair & Horace W. Stunkard. Norman R. Sinclair & Horace W. Stunkard., Aug 1970; 002572
    - Norman R. Sinclair. Norman R. Sinclair with Snowy Egret., Jun 1969; 002571
    - Norman R. Sinclair. Norman R. Sinclair., May 1969; 002568
    - Patricia Orris. Patricia Orris., Aug 1967; 002500
    - Paul A. Shave. Paul A. Shave., Jul 1967; 002550
    - Paul A. Shave. Paul A. Shave., Nov 1965; 002547
    - Paul A. Shave. Paul A. Shave., Oct 1965; 002548
    - Paul A. Shave. Paul A. Shave., Sep 1965; 002549
    - Paula L. Magilni. Paula L. Magilni., Jul 1967; 002478
    - Paula L. Magilni. Paula L. Magilni., Jul 1967; 002479
    - Paula L. Magilni. Paula L. Magilni., Jul 1967; 002480
    - Peter E. Schwamb & David C. Grant. Peter E. Schwamb & David C. Grant., Aug 1965; 002537
    - Peter E. Schwamb & David C. Grant. Peter E. Schwamb & David C. Grant., Aug 1965; 002545
    - Peter E. Schwamb & Susan Tracy. Peter E. Schwamb & Susan Tracy., Aug 1964; 002538
    - Peter E. Schwamb, Franklyn D. Ott & David C. Grant. Peter E. Schwamb. Franklyn D. Ott & David C. Grant., Nov 1965; 002536
    - Peter E. Schwamb. Peter E. Schwamb., Aug 1965; 002539
    - Peter E. Schwamb. Peter E. Schwamb., Aug 1965; 002540
    - Peter E. Schwamb. Peter E. Schwamb., May 1965; 002541
    - Peter E. Schwamb. Peter E. Schwamb., May 1965; 002542
    - Peter E. Schwamb. Peter E. Schwamb., Nov 1964; 002543